import REM1 from "./REM1.mp4"
import REM2 from "./REM2.mp4"
import REM3 from "./REM3.mp4"
import REM4 from "./REM4.mp4"
import REM5 from "./REM5.mp4"
import REM6 from "./REM6.mp4"
import REM7 from "./REM7.mp4"
import REM8 from "./REM8.mp4"
import REM9 from "./REM9.mp4"
import REM10 from "./REM10.mp4"
import REM11 from "./REM11.mp4"
import REM12 from "./REM12.mp4"
import REM13 from "./REM13.mp4"
import REM14 from "./REM14.mp4"
import REM15 from "./REM15.mp4"
import REM16 from "./REM16.mp4"
import REM17 from "./REM17.mp4"
import REM18 from "./REM18.mp4"
import REM19 from "./REM19.mp4"
import REM20 from "./REM20.mp4"
import REM21 from "./REM21.mp4"
import REM22 from "./REM22.mp4"
import REM23 from "./REM23.mp4"
import REM24 from "./REM24.mp4"
import REM25 from "./REM25.mp4"
import REM26 from "./REM26.mp4"
import REM27 from "./REM27.mp4"
import REM28 from "./REM28.mp4"
import REM29 from "./REM29.mp4"
import REM30 from "./REM30.mp4"
import REM31 from "./REM31.mp4"
import REM32 from "./REM32.mp4"
import REM33 from "./REM33.mp4"
import REM34 from "./REM34.mp4"
import REM35 from "./REM35.mp4"
import REM36 from "./REM36.mp4"
import REM37 from "./REM37.mp4"
import REM38 from "./REM38.mp4"
import REM39 from "./REM39.mp4"
import REM40 from "./REM40.mp4"
import REM41 from "./REM41.mp4"
import REM42 from "./REM42.mp4"
import REM43 from "./REM43.mp4"
import REM44 from "./REM44.mp4"
import REM45 from "./REM45.mp4"
import REM46 from "./REM46.mp4"
import REM47 from "./REM47.mp4"
import REM48 from "./REM48.mp4"
import REM49 from "./REM49.mp4"
import REM50 from "./REM50.mp4"
import REM51 from "./REM51.mp4"
import REM52 from "./REM52.mp4"
import REM53 from "./REM53.mp4"
import REM54 from "./REM54.mp4"
import REM55 from "./REM55.mp4"
import REM56 from "./REM56.mp4"
import REM57 from "./REM57.mp4"
import REM58 from "./REM58.mp4"
import REM59 from "./REM59.mp4"
import REM60 from "./REM60.mp4"
import REM61 from "./REM61.mp4"
import REM62 from "./REM62.mp4"
import REM63 from "./REM63.mp4"
import REM64 from "./REM64.mp4"
import REM65 from "./REM65.mp4"
import REM66 from "./REM66.mp4"
import REM67 from "./REM67.mp4"
import REM68 from "./REM68.mp4"
import REM69 from "./REM69.mp4"
import REM70 from "./REM70.mp4"
import REM71 from "./REM71.mp4"
import REM72 from "./REM72.mp4"
import REM73 from "./REM73.mp4"
import REM74 from "./REM74.mp4"
import REM75 from "./REM75.mp4"
import REM76 from "./REM76.mp4"



export const pulit33 = [
   
    {
        id: 771,
        videoFile: REM76,
        rusQuestion: "палатка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a shelter made of canvas or a similar material and supported by poles and ropes, that you can fold up and carry with you",
        answer: "tent",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 770,
        videoFile: REM75,
        rusQuestion: "посредственный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "not very good: ",
        answer: "mediocre",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 769,
        videoFile: REM74,
        rusQuestion: "Проваливаться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to fail to happen:",
        answer: "fall through",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 768,
        videoFile: REM73,
        rusQuestion: "артерия",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "one of the thick tubes that carry blood from the heart to other parts of the body:",
        answer: "artery",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 767,
        videoFile: REM72,
        rusQuestion: "канаста",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a card game for two to six people that is played with two sets of cards",
        answer: "canasta",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 766,
        videoFile: REM71,
        rusQuestion: "чмо",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a stupid or silly person:",
        answer: "schmuck",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 765,
        videoFile: REM70,
        rusQuestion: "испытывающий головокружение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "feeling as if everything is turning around, and that you are not able to balance and may fall over: ",
        answer: "dizzy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 764,
        videoFile: REM69,
        rusQuestion: "скрепка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a short, thin piece of wire used to fasten sheets of paper together. It has sharp ends that are pushed through the paper and then bent flat by a special device.",
        answer: "staple",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 763,
        videoFile: REM68,
        rusQuestion: "сумасшедший",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "strange, unusual, or silly:",
        answer: "loopy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 762,
        videoFile: REM67,
        rusQuestion: "заправить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an operation to remove unwanted fat from a part of the body: ",
        answer: "tuck",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 761,
        videoFile: REM66,
        rusQuestion: "отучить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to make someone gradually stop using something that is bad for them:",
        answer: "wean off",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 760,
        videoFile: REM65,
        rusQuestion: "Томография",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "abbreviation for computerized axial tomography scan: a medical test that involves using X-rays to create a three-dimensional image (= appearing to have length, width, and height) of the inside of the body:",
        answer: "cat scan",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 759,
        videoFile: REM64,
        rusQuestion: "башка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the head or mind of a person: ",
        answer: "noggin",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 758,
        videoFile: REM63,
        rusQuestion: "приставать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to touch or attack someone in a sexual way against their wishes: ",
        answer: "molest",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 757,
        videoFile: REM62,
        rusQuestion: "выбывать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to not do something that you were going to do, or to stop doing something before you have completely finished:",
        answer: "drop out",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 756,
        videoFile: REM61,
        rusQuestion: "Коричневый нос",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to try too hard to please someone, especially someone in a position of authority, in a way that other people find unpleasant: ",
        answer: "brown-nose",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 755,
        videoFile: REM60,
        rusQuestion: "неожиданно возникнуть",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to appear or happen, especially suddenly or unexpectedly: ",
        answer: "pop up",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 754,
        videoFile: REM59,
        rusQuestion: "неисправность",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to fail to work or operate correctly",
        answer: "malfunction",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 753,
        videoFile: REM58,
        rusQuestion: "отклоняющийся от нормы",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "used to describe a person or behaviour that is not usual and is generally considered to be unacceptable",
        answer: "deviant",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 752,
        videoFile: REM57,
        rusQuestion: "тайник",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to store or hide something, especially a large amount: ",
        answer: "stash",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 751,
        videoFile: REM56,
        rusQuestion: "набрать слабину",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to improve a situation by doing something that someone else has not done or not completed: ",
        answer: "pick up the slack",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 750,
        videoFile: REM55,
        rusQuestion: "солить , маринад",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a vegetable or fruit in vinegar or in salty water, especially a cucumber: ",
        answer: "pickle",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 749,
        videoFile: REM54,
        rusQuestion: "лестничная клетка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a passage in a public place with a set of steps that leads from one level to another",
        answer: "stairway",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 748,
        videoFile: REM53,
        rusQuestion: "метафора",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an expression, often found in literature, that describes a person or object by referring to something that is considered to have similar characteristics to that person or object: ",
        answer: "metaphor",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 747,
        videoFile: REM52,
        rusQuestion: "чешуйка , хлопьями ",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a small, thin piece of something, especially if it has come from a surface covered with a layer of something: ",
        answer: "flake",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 746,
        videoFile: REM51,
        rusQuestion: "злак",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a plant that is grown to produce grain: ",
        answer: "cereal",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 745,
        videoFile: REM50,
        rusQuestion: "гном",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(in old Irish stories) a magical creature in the shape of a little old man who likes to cause trouble",
        answer: "leprechaun",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 744,
        videoFile: REM49,
        rusQuestion: "шут",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a person who does silly things, usually to make other people laugh: ",
        answer: "buffoon",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 743,
        videoFile: REM48,
        rusQuestion: "клюква",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a small, round, red fruit with a sour taste",
        answer: "cranberry",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 742,
        videoFile: REM47,
        rusQuestion: "задерживаться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to take a long time to leave or disappear: ",
        answer: "linger",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 741,
        videoFile: REM46,
        rusQuestion: "печать , тюлень",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to make an agreement more certain or to approve it formally: ",
        answer: "seal",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 740,
        videoFile: REM45,
        rusQuestion: "вне чьей-то лиги",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "someone or something is too good or expensive for someone to have: ",
        answer: "out of your league",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 739,
        videoFile: REM44,
        rusQuestion: "в одиночку",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "without any help from anyone else: ",
        answer: "single-handedly",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 738,
        videoFile: REM43,
        rusQuestion: "праздничный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "celebrating an important event or a special occasion: ",
        answer: "celebratory",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 737,
        videoFile: REM42,
        rusQuestion: "смена болвана",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an amount of money that is too small to be important: ",
        answer: "chump change",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 736,
        videoFile: REM41,
        rusQuestion: "булочки",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the buttocks",
        answer: "buns",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 735,
        videoFile: REM40,
        rusQuestion: "тонкости",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a detail or small difference that is only obvious after careful thought:",
        answer: "nicety",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 734,
        videoFile: REM39,
        rusQuestion: "щель",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a straight, narrow cut or opening in something:",
        answer: "slit",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 733,
        videoFile: REM38,
        rusQuestion: "лосьон",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a liquid that you put on your skin in order to protect it, improve its condition, or make it smell pleasant: ",
        answer: "lotion",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 732,
        videoFile: REM37,
        rusQuestion: "бегун",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "someone who jogs as a form of exercise: ",
        answer: "jogger",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 731,
        videoFile: REM36,
        rusQuestion: "жеребец",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a man who is considered to be attractive and skilled sexually:",
        answer: "stud",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 730,
        videoFile: REM35,
        rusQuestion: "глупый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a person, usually a man, who is not very intelligent or attractive, or who has nothing special about him: ",
        answer: "schlub",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 729,
        videoFile: REM34,
        rusQuestion: "изящный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "good, pleasing, or effective:",
        answer: "nifty",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 728,
        videoFile: REM33,
        rusQuestion: "задобрить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to persuade someone gently to do something or go somewhere, by being kind and patient, or by appearing to be: ",
        answer: "coax",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 727,
        videoFile: REM32,
        rusQuestion: "шарады",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a team game in which each member tries to communicate to the others a particular word or phrase that they have been given, by expressing each syllable or word using silent actions:",
        answer: "charades",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 726,
        videoFile: REM31,
        rusQuestion: "ночевка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a type of party when a young person or a group of young people stay for the night at the house of a friend",
        answer: "sleepover",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 725,
        videoFile: REM30,
        rusQuestion: "реабилитация",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the process of helping someone to stop taking drugs or alcohol:",
        answer: "rehab",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 724,
        videoFile: REM29,
        rusQuestion: "зачатие",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the process of a male and a female sex cell joining and causing a baby to start to form: ",
        answer: "conception",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 723,
        videoFile: REM28,
        rusQuestion: "мягкий",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "soft and having no firm shape: ",
        answer: "mushy",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 722,
        videoFile: REM27,
        rusQuestion: "папа",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "informal US a person's buttocks.",
        answer: "heinie",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 721,
        videoFile: REM26,
        rusQuestion: "хлопать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to hit someone or something forcefully with the flat inside part of your hand, producing a short, loud noise, especially as a way of punishing a child: ",
        answer: "smack",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 720,
        videoFile: REM25,
        rusQuestion: "загрязнять",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to spoil something or someone so that that thing or person is less beautiful or pure:",
        answer: "defile",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 719,
        videoFile: REM24,
        rusQuestion: "смятение",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a feeling of unhappiness and disappointment: ",
        answer: "dismay",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 718,
        videoFile: REM23,
        rusQuestion: "сладость",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an object that people want or enjoy, often something nice to eat: ",
        answer: "goody",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 717,
        videoFile: REM22,
        rusQuestion: "битком набитый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "completely full: ",
        answer: "chock-full",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 716,
        videoFile: REM21,
        rusQuestion: "хозяин",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a person who introduces guests and performers, especially on television or radio: ",
        answer: "host",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 715,
        videoFile: REM20,
        rusQuestion: "заброшенный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "left in a particular place or condition, usually forever: ",
        answer: "abandoned",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 714,
        videoFile: REM19,
        rusQuestion: "oooo",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a man who wants to have sex a lot:",
        answer: "horndog",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 713,
        videoFile: REM18,
        rusQuestion: "скула",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "one of the two bones at the top of your cheeks, just below your eye and towards your ear: ",
        answer: "cheekbone",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 712,
        videoFile: REM17,
        rusQuestion: "хлопоты",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(a situation causing) difficulty or trouble: ",
        answer: "hassle",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 711,
        videoFile: REM16,
        rusQuestion: "операция",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the treatment of injuries or diseases in people or animals by cutting open the body and removing or repairing the damaged part: ",
        answer: "surgery",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 710,
        videoFile: REM15,
        rusQuestion: "вундеркинд",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a young person who is very smart and successful: ",
        answer: "whiz-kid",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 709,
        videoFile: REM14,
        rusQuestion: "подлый",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "doing things in a secret and unfair way: ",
        answer: "sneaky",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 708,
        videoFile: REM13,
        rusQuestion: "несвежий",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "no longer new or fresh, usually as a result of being kept for too long: ",
        answer: "stale",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 707,
        videoFile: REM12,
        rusQuestion: "откладывать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to delay an event and plan or decide that it should happen at a later date or time: ",
        answer: "postpone",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 706,
        videoFile: REM11,
        rusQuestion: "настроить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to arrange something or put its parts together in a particular form or arrangement:",
        answer: "configure",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 705,
        videoFile: REM10,
        rusQuestion: "шлюха",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an insulting word for a woman who has had a lot of sexual partners",
        answer: "hoochie",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 704,
        videoFile: REM9,
        rusQuestion: "крытый портик",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a very large room, often with glass walls or roof, especially in the middle of a large shop or office building",
        answer: "atrium",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 703,
        videoFile: REM8,
        rusQuestion: "отток",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "If you oooo something, you remove the liquid from it, usually by pouring it away or allowing it to flow away, and if something oooo, liquid flows away or out of it: ",
        answer: "drain",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 702,
        videoFile: REM7,
        rusQuestion: "переопределить",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to change the meaning of something or to make people think about something in a new or different way: ",
        answer: "redefine",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 701,
        videoFile: REM6,
        rusQuestion: "партнер",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "someone who is closely connected to another person as a companion, friend, or business partner: ",
        answer: "associate",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 700,
        videoFile: REM5,
        rusQuestion: "бороться",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to fight with someone (especially as a sport) by holding them and trying to throw them to the ground:",
        answer: "wrestle",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 699,
        videoFile: REM4,
        rusQuestion: "метранпаж",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a small device that you can press, for example to count, record, or control something, or to make a small sound: ",
        answer: "clicker",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 698,
        videoFile: REM3,
        rusQuestion: "Дистанционное управление",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a piece of equipment that you hold in your hand and use to control a television, DVD player, etc.: ",
        answer: "remote control",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 697,
        videoFile: REM2,
        rusQuestion: "шатание",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the use of a mobile phone service that you can connect to when you cannot connect to the one that you normally use, for example if you are in another country: ",
        answer: "roaming",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 696,
        videoFile: REM1,
        rusQuestion: "мерцать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "(of light or a shiny surface) to shine repeatedly strongly then weakly, as if flashing on and off very quickly: ",
        answer: "twinkle",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        try: 1,
        getHight: 1
    },
]